[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal does Jane put in her sisters dish in the 1962 movie What Ever Happened to Baby Jane??", "correct_answer": "Rat", "incorrect_answers": ["Frog", "Cockroach", "Snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sides of a triangle are 1 inch, 2 inches and 3 inches. What is the perimeter of the triangle.", "correct_answer": "It has no perimeter", "incorrect_answers": ["6 cubic inches", "6 square inches", "6 inches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the older nerds in the movie The Benchwarmers was once a bully.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which British band performed the song Champagne Supernova that was included in the album (Whats the Story) Morning Glory?", "correct_answer": "Oasis", "incorrect_answers": ["The Who", "Blur", "The Police"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Lydia Litvyak?", "correct_answer": "The top female fighter ace of World War II", "incorrect_answers": ["The first female to get an engineering degree in the USA", "The first Polish woman chief of state", "The inventor of the silicon chip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nicholas Cage co-wrote parts of the script of the 2007 film Ghost Rider.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this slogan which advertises a candy bar: A _______ a day helps you work, rest and play", "correct_answer": "Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["Kit Kat", "Snickers", "Twix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the three brothers as adults in the 1939 version of Beau Geste, directed by William Wellman?", "correct_answer": "Gary Cooper, Ray Milland, and Robert Preston", "incorrect_answers": ["Gary Cooper, Ray Milland, and Brian Donleavy", "Ray Milland, Brian Donleavy, and Albert Dekker", "Gary Cooper, Brian Donleavy, and Albert Dekker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which line contains only types of precipitation?", "correct_answer": "Graupel, sleet, snow, hail", "incorrect_answers": ["Snow, vapor, fog drip, hail", "Rain, fog drip, runoff, sleet", "Snow, ice, hail, rain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full name of UTC, the company that manufactures Sikorsky helicopters?", "correct_answer": "United Technologies Corporation", "incorrect_answers": ["United Tennessee Company", "Union of high-Technology Corporations", "Union of Texas Craft-makers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lentils and beans are rich in fiber, omega-3 acids and calcium.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is the number one predator of zebras?", "correct_answer": "Lion", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackal", "Hyena", "Crocodile"]}]